***********************
ha! A Corps! What are you doing? ?
Blast out!
Everyone be quiet! Listen to what he has to say first!
Three beauties, I am from the A Corps. Although we have had festivals before, I am not here to make trouble this time.
Our boss, the strongest fighter in the East, brother Andy
Invite everyone to stay at the A Corps station three days later, and we will publish the secret documents in Noah’s Arsenal!
What is that... It’s so troublesome to say...
Those guys from Noah said so horribly, I wanted to curse them to death a long time ago!
I know your boss, he is a handsome guy, and his personality is not bad.
The A Corps is now well-known far and wide, and we agree to attend the appointment!
***********************
Who is coming? 
I am from the A Corps. Although we have had festivals before, but this time I come...
I know you are not here to make trouble, my master has already calculated that someone who is destined to come will come today, please follow me!
What?
Do you know that I have never been defeated in martial arts competitions in my life!
Master, last time you were injured!
I didn’t come to fight you today...
shut up! I didn’t say I want to fight you, what are you afraid of?
Master, I really don’t understand you, why didn’t you kill this kid! Have you forgotten your previous hatred? !
What do you know, this kid is human, and the people from the A Corps who are against us are also human!
Do you know who our real enemy is?
It’s Noah’s guys, they’re not human at all! They are not of this world...
Heck, can I chime in? I’m here to say...
Needless to say! I will be there in three days!
That Andy guy...I want to have a sparring with him too...wahahahahahaha! ! ! !
You won’t mess around, will you?
(How does this guy know?!)
see a visitor out! !
***********************
stop, who?
Everyone, I am from the A Corps. Although we have had festivals before, I am not here to ask for trouble this time.
Our boss, the strongest fighter in the East, brother Andy
Invite everyone to stay at the A Corps station three days later, and we will publish the secret documents in Noah’s Arsenal!
May I ask who is your chief now? I need to speak to your chief!
No... Noah! ! You destroyed Noah’s territory? !
Could it be that Noah who bloodbathed our base before? !
Exactly! After we captured their arsenal, we got a backup hard drive, which has been decrypted successfully!
Quick... quick! Notify the commander!
yes! !
The hunting dog calls the queen, the hunting dog calls the queen, the password, the dog jumps over the wall in a hurry!
commander in chief! The A Corps is here...
No, not looking for trouble!They cracked Noah’s confidential information.
Invite you to discuss with the A Corps resident in three days!
……… Mmm…, Mmmm…
The commander asked me to tell you that he agreed to attend the appointment!
Hmm... I don’t know who the new commander is...
***********************
Well…………………
Oh, here comes the thieves.
KING, hold your gun, don’t let it go, these guys are guests!
Ah, seeing these noisy guys makes me angry...
Ah... aren’t these the guys I cursed all the time?
Hmm... It looks like a guy who is almost as weird as us...
Hi! Little ones! Lower the gun! Here we are!
Are you ready to rock and roll?
Have a chance to come to a 3VS3 match!
Let’s see if our BPK team is the best or your rock park is the best!
But not today! Please come with us!
thanks! brothers! come with us!
oh!
oh……
Is this the legendary base of the A Corps? Well... Although it looks inconspicuous, the security arrangement is very good.
It seems that it is only natural that you were unable to capture this place last time.
Commander, do we want to occupy this place this time?
You idiot! The current A Corps is no longer the small organization it was back then!
A Noah’s guy almost wiped out us all, but the A Corps can destroy Noah’s territory and get information...
That’s why I come here because it’s safer here!
Long time no see, General... I heard that you have been killed by an Ark warrior! Didn’t expect to see you again!
Hehe...that’s just a substitute for me! Since then, I have been hiding in the most hidden place in the desert!
Really leisurely! But your strategy is correct, at least you saved your life. Inside please!
please! !
I really don’t understand, isn’t that guy in green the boss here?
We once attacked here, and he took out one of our divisions himself. Why didn’t he and the general mention it?
You know what a fart! Just protect the general!
Master, that boy Andy is not here!
Huh? There’s a punching bag guy over there!
He didn’t seem to be in the least alarmed by our arrival.
Aren’t the A Corps all playing with guns? What does it mean to be unarmed? Pterosaur, go try him!
Here!
Sure enough, he is a master! Worthy of being the A Corps!
Are you from the Black Iron Society? Since you have been invited to discuss major issues, why don’t you go the right way?
Disturb me clean up!
Isn’t this Andy’s room? Wouldn’t it be easy for me to come here directly!
Now that the Black Iron Society has arrived, let me lead the way, this way please!
rock park
warlord
black iron club
Hi! Andy! Why is this hateful general here? Isn’t he dead?
Little sister, you are confused about the situation, the gathering of the four major organizations today is not for our past grievances!
Although you thieves are the weakest, hahahahaha!
What? !
okay! We Black Iron will come here just to obtain information! I’m not here to listen to you weaklings babbling!
The leader of the A Corps, Andy, you are the initiator of this rally, let’s you speak!
Everyone! Since Judgment Day, how many relatives, friends, and lovers have left us!
there’s only us! It is difficult to linger on this scorched earth! Continue the history of mankind!
However, all this is the result of being manipulated! 
ha? impossible? !
This... Although we were the first to come into contact with the warriors of the Ark, Judgment Day was manipulated, isn’t this too ridiculous?
...I had an ominous premonition long ago, but it was like chaos, making me unable to see clearly...
When the end comes, we will naturally think of Noah’s Ark recorded in the Bible,
The huge hull will be filled with species from all over the world to continue the civilization of the earth, while other creatures who are not on board will die in the disaster!
This legend is actually not so beautiful! Because we are all those who are not on board!
This...I’m so cute, why no one asked me to board the boat!
so funny! Andy, is that what you guys want us to hear from you? !
I have a vague feeling that even the creatures saved by the Ark will be a trip to hell...
Our A Corps has fought against Noah more than all of you here. We got a backup hard drive after destroying their transformed zombie arsenal.
After deciphering, we found that it contained a large amount of extraterrestrial life data! I call it ”Reaper of Civilization”.
every few thousand years,
The civilization reaper will come to the earth,
Harvest the species and technologies evolved at that time,
Then wipe out all creatures and civilizations on the earth,
so that at the next harvest,
Can harvest new species and civilizations.
understand? It’s like farming!
The time span of many civilization monuments discovered by human beings is very ancient.
Judging from the various relics of prehistoric human civilizations excavated and discovered today,
From a very long time ago,
Humans have always existed on our planet,
And developed a highly developed civilization.
For example, human footprints wearing shoes found on trilobite fossils from 600 million to 250 million years ago,
A 2-billion-year-old large chain nuclear reactor discovered in what is today Gabon, Africa,
A 2.8-billion-year-old metal ball found in what is now South Africa,
and many stone tools of different periods, etc.,
There have been many prehistoric humans and civilizations on the earth.
Human development is not as previously imagined,
but cyclically,
Different civilizations existed on Earth in different periods.
And why is it cyclical?
It is because of the existence of the Civilization Reaper! !
understand? That’s why dinosaurs suddenly disappeared,
Why did the ancient Egyptian civilization,
Atlantis and other prehistoric civilizations,
The reason will disappear!
Because it was wiped out by the Civilization Reaper!
That is to say, the end of the world this time is the result of civilization harvesters wanting to erase all life and civilization again?
And the more powerful the organization, the more disaster it will suffer!
So what does the Civilization Reaper look like?
And our survival is not good for them!
Yes, the Civilization Reapers use apocalypse to destroy most of the biological life and most of the technological civilization, and then use the modified zombies to deal with the surviving life,
In the end, this civilization will be completely wiped out...it will not pollute the environment, and then help mankind build a new civilization again, and become the god of mankind again...
But we who know its true face may have been wiped out by then...
I cannot allow this to happen! Otherwise, how can I be worthy of the ancestors under the Nine Springs!
At present, the true face of the Civilization Reaper is still unclear, because all the pictures and videos in the cracked data have been processed. But we already know the location of Noah’s Ark!
Noah’s strength is unfathomable... He has successfully wiped out so many human civilizations in history... Can we do it with just a few of us...
Anyway, our thieves must be auxiliary! How many of you are the main force...
In addition to the fact that our 4 major organizations must join forces, we also need to unite all forces that can be united! Andy, do you have any countermeasures to stop this erasure?
To stop this obliteration, our intelligence is not enough!
The current clear information is that Noah’s Ark is hiding in the southern plateau snow-capped mountains. Find Noah’s Ark and get the necessary information!
I need everyone to attack Noah’s various arsenals and bases to buy time for the A Corps. The A Corps will go straight to the snow-capped mountains to find Noah’s Ark and information!
Our thieves group has the most eyes, and I will be responsible for finding Noah’s base!
Our legion can be responsible for destroying monsters that transform zombies.
If there are rare transformed zombies, or masters such as Ark Warriors, Ark Beastmasters, etc., we must leave them to Black Iron Society to solve them! This is a rare opportunity to practice!
Come, this glass of wine, for our four major organizations to join forces to form a ”Doomsday Alliance” to defend world peace, cheers!
cheers!
I am really happy today, I can make friends with a few brothers, and we thieves will have a better life in the future!
When we get through the crisis smoothly, all of us must go to Fallen City to watch your rock park concert!
I didn’t expect that there would be a day of counterattack, I thought I would hide in the desert for the rest of my life! I thought about it early to get some air!
I’ll come to you again, Andy Law, no one can stop me from dominating the world!
I’m waiting for you!
Goodbye, everyone!
Goodbye!